# The heatmap module makes it simple to make your own heatmaps in PowerShell
# You can make a heatmap out of any performance counter that uses a percentage.
# Let's start out with the simplest heatmap, % processor time
Add-HeatmapCounter '\Processor(*)\% Processor Time'

# Running Add-HeatmapCounter checks that the counter exists, and adds it to a list of heatmap items
# to see the current heatmap counters, check out 
Get-HeatmapCounter

# To watch the heatmap, simply use
Watch-Heatmap

# To watch the heatmap for ever (or until you press CTRL+C), use
Watch-Heatmap -Continuous 

